lensshopper.com 2007-05-26

# Privacy Policy for Lensshopper.com

Privacy Policy - Lensshopper.com! 

Any information you furnish to Lensshopper.com will be kept with utmost care. It will not be used in any ways that you yourself have not explicitly agreed to. Any user data that is gathered by this web site will remain strictly confidential. We will not sell, rent, loan, reuse, or in any other way reveal it to any third party. Lensshopper.com will always respect your privacy.

**1\. Data collected through the visitor’s browser**  
We at Lensshopper.com use our web site logs to estimate the worth of different materials we put up on the site. The data in the logs can never be connected to individual persons, and we never try to associate any piece of information to the actual persons visiting the site.

**2\. Disclosure of information to third parties**  
Lensshopper.com does not sell, rent, loan, reuse, or in any other way reveal any personal information gathered by the site. This includes lists of email addresses and membership blanks. 

**3\. Using cookies**  
Lensshopper.com utilize so called cookies on the web site, generally with the intention of following up how visitors move between our site and other web sites. We never try to connect any cookie information to individual persons or extract any piece of personal data from this input.

**4\. Web site ads**  
The Lensshopper.com site currently features a number of advertisements that are managed by proprietary software, which comply to those privacy guidelines.

**5\. Disclaimer**  
Lensshopper.com reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. We suggest that interested visitors check the following url on a regular basis: http://www.Lensshopper.com/privacy-policy.asp

Please submit any questions or comments by email to the following address: info@Lensshopper.com.
